gamezebo.com 2013-04-12

# Privacy Policy | Gamezebo

Please take a moment to read our privacy policy prior to using this Website 

This privacy statement ("Privacy Policy") covers all the websites owned, affiliated or operated by Gamezebo, Inc. ("Gamezebo", "we", "us", "our"). Gamezebo knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the Gamezebo websites, submitting information or using any of our products or services, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

We want to share with you how we treat personal information about you that we receive in connection with this Website.

Also, note that use of this Website is governed by the Terms of Service posted on the Website. As noted in the Terms of Service, Gamezebo expressly excludes any representation or warranty, express or implied, with respect to the information available on this Website. Gamezebo makes no representation about any third-party websites that may be accessed via links from this Website. By using this Website, you agree that the laws of the State of California, without regard to its conflict of laws principles, will govern all matters between you and Gamezebo with respect to your use of this Website.  

### What does Gamezebo do?

Gamezebo is an online web site and community obsessed with casual games. We post reviews, previews, strategy guides, news, and articles about casual games. In addition, we let you post your own ratings and reviews on casual games, comment in our forums, and meet and interact with others like you who are passionate about playing casual games.

### What Information We Collect and How We Use It?

In general, you can visit our Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, in order to provide the best online service and enrich our members' experience, as described further below, sections of this Website may request and display some of your personal information to other members and visitors. Gamezebo members can change their profile information at any time and can control how we and other members communicate with them.

Gamezebo collects personal information that you may submit to us for such purposes as becoming a member of Gamezebo and registering for the use of certain restricted portions of this Website. We use this information to help authenticate users of Gamezebo, send you and other members newsletters and notifications regarding our services, respond to your requests for information or other materials, conduct internal analyses such as surveys, and help you to identify and communicate with other members. Our use of email addresses is discussed in greater detail below in the section entitled “What About Email Addresses.” Note, only your “user name” which you pick is displayed on this Web site. Your full name is never displayed by Gamezebo to other members (unless you expressy pick it as your user name, disclose it in a User review or a forum).

Gamezebo has a general policy of not disclosing your personal information to third parties unless you have consented to such sharing. However, we may share the personal information you provide to us with trusted companies we have hired to provide services for us, such as sending out newsletters, developing new Web site features, or collecting or processing information on our behalf. These companies - our vendors - are contractually bound to use personal information that we share with them only to perform the services we have hired them to provide.

In addition, through certain technologies, Gamezebo also collects non-personally-identifiable information from users and visitors to this site. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third parties to provide more relevant services and targeted advertisements to members. For more information on how we collect this type of information, please see the section below entitled “What about Cookies.”

User profile information which may include your picture and user name (that you provide us) is displayed to other members in order to facilitate user interaction within the Gamezebo community. You can modify and change your personal information at any time by logging into your account, going to your my Gamezebo page, and clicking “Edit my Account.”

### What About Email Addresses?

When you provide your email address, we may use it for the purposes of facilitating your invitations to new friends (“Invitees”) to join Gamezebo, inviting “friends” to connect to your personal My Gamezebo page, and sending notifications and other communications related to the Services, such as, for example, newsletters, emailing an article to a friend, or other information. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, or emailing an article to a friend, we will not share or display your email address. We will only do the above is initiated by the user.

Gamezebo members can invite Invitees to join the service by sending emails via our automated invitation system. Gamezebo does not sell the email addresses of Invitees and uses them solely for the internal purposes of sending email invitations and invitation reminders. 

### Can I Opt Out of Emails?

Members who no longer wish to receive notifications or other communications via email may opt out of such communications. Go to your My Gamezebo Page, click “Edit my Account,” click “Edit Account Settings, and then select to change your email settings.

### What about Cookies?

A “cookie” is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing non-personally identifiable information about you. We may use cookies in order to collect certain information about you, such as IP addresses (e.g., whether you are logged on from a .com, .gov, or .edu domain), domain names (the Internet address of a computer), browser type, and the type of computer and operating system being used. Gamezebo uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information to ensure that visitors are provided with a customized content and advertising experience. We record your IP address for security and monitoring purposes.

We do not link the information stored in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to change your cookie settings. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you certain features available on this Website. To disable all cookies, follow the instructions for your particular browser. 

### Customized Advertisements, Promotions, and Sweepstakes

Ads appearing on this Website may be delivered to users by Gamezebo or one of our Web advertising partners. As noted above, we may use cookies to provide you with customized, targeted ads. Our Web advertising partners may also set cookies or pixel tags (also called “clear GIFs” or “beacons”) to allow their ad servers to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information such as whether you saw their advertisements and which ads you “clicked” on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Please note, however, that this privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Gamezebo on this website and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy policies, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

In addition, from time to time, Gamezebo or a partner may sponsor a promotion, sweepstakes or contest on Gamezebo. If you voluntarily participate in these activities, you may be asked to provide personal information including your name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. If you participate in a promotion, sweepstakes, or contest, we may transfer personal information to our ad partners who have sponsored the promotions, sweepstakes, or contests. It will be clear at the point of collection whether Gamezebo or one of our sponsors or advertising partners is collecting your personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

### Links to Third Party Web Sites

We may provide links to third party websites as a convenience to you. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Gamezebo. Gamezebo is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on these linked sites. When linking to another site, you should read the privacy policy posted on that linked site.

### Public Information

Whenever you voluntarily post public information anywhere on the Gamezebo Web site, people can access that information and in turn could use that information to send you unsolicited communications. Do not post information you consider to be private on this Website if you desire to maintain the privacy of that information.

### How Old Should I Be?

The magic age is 13 or above. Gamezebo does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible.

### Security

At Gamezebo, your privacy and security are our top priorities. Accounts are secured by member-created passwords.

Gamezebo takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database and restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff.

PLEASE NOTE: we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time.

### Privacy and Sharing

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Gamezebo will never disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Gamezebo, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Gamezebo Terms of Use Agreement and to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the Gamezebo service.

Gamezebo reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of all or substantially all of Gamezebo’ assets to that successor in interest. For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.

### Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit Gamezebo, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Services, including limitation of damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.

### Changes in Our Privacy Policy

We may make changes to our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will inform users of any changes we make by posting a notice on our Website. USERS WILL ALWAYS BE AWARE OF THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT VIA THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

If you are a Member, we will attempt to inform you of any modifications to this Privacy Policy that affect (a) your obligations to Gamezebo or our obligations to you either by sending you an email at the email address you provided as part of the registration process, or by a message to you at the time you log into the Gamezebo Site. If you do not agree with any such modifications, your sole remedy is the termination of your Membership, which you may request by sending an email to [privacy@gamezebo.com](mailto:privacy@Gamezebo.com). Your continued use of the Service after receiving notice of any modifications indicates your acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy. 

If you are a Visitor, any modifications to this Privacy Policy will be effective as to you upon Gamezebo posting the new terms and/or upon implementation of the new changes on the Gamezebo Site. You agree to review this Privacy Policy periodically so that you are aware of any modifications. Your continued use of the Service after any modifications indicates your acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy.

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy, feel free to contact us at [privacy@gamezebo.com](mailto:privacy@gamezebo.com).
